(Penny:)Come on, let's just
get this over with.
"Let's get this over with."
(Leonard:)Am I driving you
to the Cheesecake Factory,
(Leonard:)or are we having sex?
I'm just trying to lighten the mood.
(Penny:)-I know. Thank you.
-Sorry.
(Penny:)It's just so humiliating.
(Leonard:)So humiliating?
(Leonard:)Am I driving you to
the Cheesecake Factory....?
(Penny:)I'm sorry.
I'll stop. I'll stop.
(Leonard:)Come on, don't look so sad.
You never know what's gonna happen.
(Leonard:)Maybe tonight will be great.
(Penny:)Sweetie, I know you're trying
to make me feel better,
(Penny:)and I love you for that,
but it's making me feel worse,
(Penny:)and I kind of hate you.
(Penny:)This isn't your car.
(Leonard:)I know. I thought we'd take yours.
(Penny:)I don't understand.
(Leonard:)It's nothing fancy,
but it'll get you to auditions,
(Leonard:)and at least for now, you don't
have to go back to waitressing.
(Penny:)I don't know what to say.
(Leonard:)Don't say anything.
(Penny:)Oh, my God.